Guide to the Robert Ensko Inc. Records 1787-1798, 1908-1978 (bulk 1934-1970) MS 200
New-York Historical Society
- Series IV. Client Lists & Related Records, 1937-1970; 12.5 Linear feet
  - Index cards: Pre-1960 clients (Box 1 of 5), 1930s-1960s (Offsite-box 109)
    This set of 5 boxes includes index cards from the 1930s-50s with a record of clients and their purchases, presumably no longer active in 1960 and later (see "current clients" above). The cards also include those from the 1960s that moved into these inactive cards at some point. Also, for some major clients, like New York Racing Association, these cards include their older transactions even though they remained active/current clients in the 1960s. This box holds cards for clients with names beginning A-COP. Cards under C include "cash sales."
  - Index cards: Pre-1960 clients (Box 2 of 5), 1930s-1960s (Offsite-box 110)
    This box holds cards with client names beginning COR-HARP.
  - Index cards: Pre-1960 clients (Box 3 of 5), 1930s-1960s (Offsite-box 111)
    This box holds cards with names beginning HARR-Mc (not Mac or M general).
  - Index cards: Pre-1960 clients (Box 4 of 5), 1930s-1960s (Offsite-box 112)
    This box holds cards with names beginning M (except Mc)- RO.
  - Index cards: Pre-1960 clients (Box 5 of 5), 1930s-1960s (Offsite-box 113)
    This box holds cards with names beginning RU-WIL. This is the end of the set.
- Series V. Sales Tickets and Invoices, 1941-1970; 87 Linear feet
  The series includes hundreds of thousands of two overlapping documents: customer transaction tickets and customer invoices. Transaction tickets record client/customer object sales, repairs, engravings, and other client-related matters such as returns and credit memos. Data on the tickets include client name and address, object or service purchased, stock number, price, transaction and shipment date, shipping address, and other pertinent details.
  There is a high degree of redundancy in the series because there are as many as three copies of the tickets: one arranged and bound in alphabetical order by client, one arranged by ticket number (very roughly chronological), and for some, a third (pink color) copy. Nonetheless, for the earliest records in the series, from the early 1940s, there is only one copy of the ticket.
  The invoices are carbon copies of the originals sent to customers. The invoices include much of the same information found on the tickets, but in much more polished form. The tickets are handwritten, often with detailed working notes and customer specifications. The invoices are typed lists or straightforward notes of the item or service purchased.
  Taken together, the documents appear to be a comprehensive, detailed view of Ensko's client transactions.
  A detailed understanding of the interrelationship of these documents and others from the business can be gleaned from a 1954 "Client order procedure" found in Series IV (Box 75). This was a procedural document apparently written for a new typist. The essentials of it seem to be relevant for tickets from the 1940s on through 1970.
  The series is organized by the three overall sales transaction-related sets of documents in the collection:
  Series V.A. Sales Tickets by Client (1946-1970)
  Series V.B. Sales Tickets by Ticket Number (1941-1970)
  Series V.C. Client Invoices (1946-1970)
  - Subseries V.A. Sales Tickets by Client, 1946-1970; 22 Linear feet
    The subseries includes copies of sales tickets bound in alphabetical order by client by year. A major client, New York Racing Association (NYRA), seems to appear for the first time in 1958. For some years, NYRA tickets were bound separately; in other years they are simply filed with the other letter N clients.
    There are a total of 314 booklets of tickets and is a complete run from 1946 to 1969. 1970 is missing one of its three booklets. The breakdown by year is: 1946 (6 booklets), 1947 (11), 1948 (12), 1949 (12), 1950 (14), 1951 (14), 1952 (10), 1953 (11), 1954 (15), 1955 (17), 1956 (16), 1957 (16), 1958 (14), 1959 (12), 1960 (20), 1961 (17), 1962 (24), 1963 (19), 1964 (14), 1965 (11), 1966 (9), 1967 (7), 1968 (7), 1969 (4), and 1970 (3).
    - Booklets: 1946 (all clients); 1946 (A-L), 1946-1947 (Offsite-box 83)
    - Booklets: 1947 (M-Z); 1948 (A-R), 1947-1948 (Offsite-box 84)
    - Booklets: 1948 (S-Z); 1949 (all clients), 1948-1949 (Offsite-box 85)
    - Booklets: 1950 (all clients) (Offsite-box 86)
    - Booklets: 1951 (all clients) (Offsite-box 87)
    - Booklets: 1952 (all clients) (Offsite-box 88)
    - Booklets: 1953 (all clients); 1954 (A-C), 1953-1954 (Offsite-box 89)
    - Booklets: 1954 (D-Z) (Offsite-box 90)
    - Booklets: 1955 (A-S) (Offsite-box 91)
    - Booklets: 1955 (T-Z); 1956 (A-P), 1955-1956 (Offsite-box 92)
    - Booklets: 1956 (R-Z); 1957 (A-M), 1956-1957 (Offsite-box 93)
    - Booklets: 1957 (N-Z); 1958 (A-K), 1957-1958 (Offsite-box 94)
    - Booklets: 1958 (L-Z); 1959 (A-K), 1958-1959 (Offsite-box 95)
    - Booklets: 1959 (L-Z); 1960 (A-M), 1959-1960 (Offsite-box 96)
    - Booklets: 1960 (M-Z); 1961 (A-L), 1960-1961 (Offsite-box 97)
    - Booklets: 1961 (M-Z); 1962 (A-G), 1961-1962 (Offsite-box 98)
    - Booklets: 1962 (H-Z); 1963 (A-B), 1962-1963 (Offsite-box 99)
    - Booklets: 1963 (C-Z) (Offsite-box 100)
    - Booklets: 1964 (all clients) (Offsite-box 101)
    - Booklets: 1965 (all clients); 1966 (A-L), 1965-1966 (Offsite-box 102)
    - Booklets: 1966 (M-Z); 1967 (all clients), 1966-1967 (Offsite-box 103)
    - Booklets: 1968 (all clients); 1969 (all clients); 1970 (H-Z), 1968-1970 (Offsite-box 104)
      1970 is missing one booklet of tickets, for names beginning A-G. In addition to the booklets, there is an envelope of tickets for 1969-1970.
  - Subseries V.B. Sales Tickets by Ticket Number, 1941-1970; 39 Linear feet
    The subseries includes tickets documenting Robert Ensko Inc's sales, repairs, credits, and other client transactions. These are the same tickets as those in Subseries V.A., except that 1) the tickets in this subseries extend back to 1941-1945, which those in subseries V.A. do not and 2) these tickets are arranged in ticket number order, not by client/customer. It is also unknown if perhaps certain details are on one set of the tickets and not the other. For tickets dating from 1957-1970, the subseries includes a duplicate set (pink color form).
    The subseries is arranged in very rough chronological order. It retains the documents' original order, which is by pre-stamped sequential ticket number. These sequence numbers do not strictly correspond to transaction chronology. It appears that, at least in the mid-1940s and later, multiple ticket books were in use at any one time and that within an order book, transactions were recorded on pages more or less at random. So transactions for a particular period of time can be found at various points in the order ticket sequence. Except for the earliest tickets, which are in booklets, the used tickets were secured together in thick stacks of a 1000 or more in two-pronged binders. The container list records the sequence numbers of each of these stacks and the approximate date range of each stack. The date range was determined by quick skims by the processing archivist and its precision is uncertain.
    The documents make it apparent that Ensko used one run of sequence numbers from 1941 to 1958, and then restarted the numbering in 1958. This second run was used until the business closed in 1970. The container list distinguishes between this "1st run" and "2nd run."
    The bulk of the duplicate (pink) copies of the tickets in the subseries pertain to the 2nd run and are presented in the container list after the primary copy. The few pink copies that pertain to the 1st run are listed after that.
    - Sales tickets. 1st run, 1941-1958. (Box 1 of 19), 1941-1942 (Offsite-box 121)
      Includes tickets #100-3675, held in booklets numbered 1-48. Date range January 1941-December 1942.
    - Sales tickets. 1st run, 1941-1958. (Box 2 of 19), 1942-1944 (Offsite-box 122)
      Includes tickets #3676-6966, held in booklets numbered 49-82. Date range December 1942 to October 1944.
    - Sales tickets. 1st run, 1941-1958. (Box 3 of 19), 1943-1946 (Offsite-box 123)
      Includes tickets #6967-9768, held in booklets numbered 83-96 (ends the run of this form of booklet, though the ticket number sequence continues). Date range October 1944-January 1946. This box also holds two books, numbered 8 and 9 with ticket slips dating from June 1943-April 1944; these tickets differ from those of the main 1st run, but the relationship between them is unclear.
    - Sales tickets. 1st run, 1941-1958. (Box 4 of 19), 1945-1947 (Offsite-box 124)
      This box holds loose and bundled packets of unprocessed blue copies of tickets, dating from 1945-1947. It is unclear how these relate to the main 1st run tickets, but may simply be additional copies.
    - Sales tickets. 1st run, 1941-1958. (Box 5 of 19), 1946-1947 (Offsite-box 125)
      Continuing from Box 123, this box includes tickets #9769-10794, held in a new form of booklet numbered 1-6. Date range January 1946-May 1946. This ends this short run of this form of booklet and there is a gap in the ticket number sequence before picking up again. There is no apparent gap however in the date range, so the numerical gap may or may not indicate the absence of transaction records. This box then holds the further continuation of the ticket sequence. From here, all tickets in the subseries (with minor exception) are no longer held in booklets, but in thick stacks held together in two-pronged enclosures. This box holds 3 stacks: tickets 11701-12400 (June 1946-August 1946), (gap), 14701-16000 (March 1947-June 1947), 16000-17099 (July 1947-October 1947).
    - Sales tickets. 1st run, 1941-1958. (Box 6 of 19), 1947-1948 (Offsite-box 126)
      This box holds 5 stacks: tickets 17100-17999 (Oct 1947-Dec 1947), 18000-18999 (June 1947-March 1948), 19000-19700 (March 1948-May 1948), 19701-20350 (May 1948-July 1948), 20351-21699 (July 1948-Nov 1948).
    - Sales tickets. 1st run, 1941-1958. (Box 7 of 19), 1948-1949 (Offsite-box 127)
      This box holds 5 stacks: tickets 21700-21999 (Nov 1948-Dec 1948), 22000-22999 (Dec 1948-Jan 1949 and some later), 23000-23999 (Jan 1949-May 1949), 24000-24999 (April 1949-August 1949), 25000-25999 (July 1949-Nov 1949).
    - Sales tickets. 1st run, 1941-1958. (Box 8 of 19), 1949-1950 (Offsite-box 128)
      This box holds 4 stacks: tickets 26000-26999 (Nov 1949-March 1950), 27000-27999 (Jan 1950-May 1950), 28000-28999 (April 1950-June 1950), 29000-29999 (June 1950-Oct 1950).
    - Sales tickets. 1st run, 1941-1958. (Box 9 of 19), 1950-1952 (Offsite-box 129)
      This box holds 5 stacks: tickets 30000-30999 (Oct 1950-Dec 1950), 31000-31999 (Nov 1950-Feb 1951), 32000-32999 (Jan 1951-March 1951), 33000-33678 (March 1951-April 1951), and 36000-36999 (May 1951-Jan 1952). There is a gap with no tickets 33679-35499. See next box for 35500-35999.
    - Sales tickets. 1st run, 1941-1958. (Box 10 of 19), 1951-1952 (Offsite-box 130)
      This box holds 5 stacks: tickets 35500-35999 (May 1951-June 1951), (see above box for 36000-36999), 37000-37999 (August 1951-Oct 1951), 38000-38999 (Oct 1951-Dec 1951), 39000-39999 (Dec 1951-April 1952), 40000-40999 (March 1952-July 1952).
    - Sales tickets. 1st run, 1941-1958. (Box 11 of 19), 1951?-1953 (Offsite-box 131)
      This box holds 4 stacks: tickets 41000-41999 (May 1952-Sept 1952), 42000-42999 (July 1952-Oct 1952), 43000-43999 (Oct 1952-Jan 1953) (some tickets in this stack seem to be dated from Nov 1951), 44000-44999 (Nov 1952-Feb 1953).
    - Sales tickets. 1st run, 1941-1958. (Box 12 of 19), 1953-1954 (Offsite-box 132)
      This box holds 4 stacks: tickets 45000-45999 (Jan 1953-April 1953), 46000-46999 (March 1953-June 1953), 47000-47999 (June 1953-Oct 1953), 48000-48999 (August 1953-Jan 1954).
    - Sales tickets. 1st run, 1941-1958. (Box 13 of 19), 1953-1954 (Offsite-box 133)
      This box holds 4 stacks: tickets 49000-49999 (Oct 1953-Jan 1954), 50000-50999 (Dec 1953-April 1954), 51000-51999 (March 1954-June 1954), 52000-52999 (June 1954-August 1954).
    - Sales tickets. 1st run, 1941-1958. (Box 14 of 19), 1954-1955 (Offsite-box 134)
      This box holds 4 stacks: tickets 53000-53999 (July 1954-Oct 1954), 54000-54999 (Oct 1954-Dec 1954), 55000-55999 (Oct 1954-May 1955), 56000-56999 (Jan 1955-May 1955).
    - Sales tickets. 1st run, 1941-1958. (Box 15 of 19), 1955-1956 (Offsite-box 135)
      This box holds 4 stacks: tickets 57000-57999 (April 1955-June 1955), 58000-58999 (June 1955-Sept 1955), 59000-59999 (August 1955-Nov 1955), 60000-60999 (Sept 1955-Jan 1956).
    - Sales tickets. 1st run, 1941-1958. (Box 16 of 19), 1955-1956 (Offsite-box 136)
      This box holds 4 stacks: tickets 61000-61999 (Nov 1955-March 1956), 62000-62999 (Jan 1956-July 1956), 63000-63999 (March 1956-Oct 1956), 64000-64999 (June 1956-Oct 1956).
    - Sales tickets. 1st run, 1941-1958. (Box 17 of 19), 1956-1957 (Offsite-box 137)
      This box holds 4 stacks: tickets 65000-65999 (May 1956-Feb 1957), 66000-66999 (Sept 1956-Jan 1957), 67000-67999 (Dec 1956-March 1957), 68000-68999 (Feb 1957-May 1957).
    - Sales tickets. 1st run, 1941-1958. (Box 18 of 19), 1957-1958 (Offsite-box 138)
      This box holds 4 stacks: tickets 69000-69999 (May 1957-Sept 1957), 70000-70999 (June 1957-Sept 1957), 71000-71999 (Sept 1957-Nov 1957), 72000-72999 (Nov 1957-Feb 1958).
    - Sales tickets. 1st run, 1941-1958. (Box 19 of 19), 1957-1958 (Offsite-box 139)
      This box holds the final 3 stacks of tickets comprising the main copies of the 1st run: tickets 73000-73999 (Nov 1957-April 1958), 74000-74999 (April 1958-June 1958), 75000-75500 (May 1958-July 1958).
    - Sales tickets. 1st run, 1941-1958, pink copy. (Box 1 of 2), 1955-1957 (Offsite-box 158)
      These two boxes hold a limited number of the pink (duplicate) copy of the sales tickets, 1st run. The bulk are from 1957-58, but a few random tickets go back to 1955 and 1956. This box holds 3 stacks of tickets: tickets 67105-68999 (1955-57), 69000-70699 (1957), and 70701-721999 (1957).
    - Sales tickets. 1st run, 1941-1958, pink copy. (Box 2 of 2), 1957-1958 (Offsite-box 159)
      This box holds the final 3 stacks of tickets comprising the pink copies of the 1st run: This box holds 3 stacks of tickets: tickets 72200-73199 (1957-58), 73200-74199 (1958), and 74200-75500 (1958).
    - Sales tickets. 2nd run, 1958-1970. (Box 1 of 11) (Offsite-box 139)
      In this 2nd run, the ticket numbering restarts with 100, but continues chronologically with no gap from the 1st run that ended with ticket 75500 in July 1958. This box holds 2 stacks: tickets 100-999 (July 1958-Oct 1958) and 1000-1999 (Sept 1958-Dec 1958).
    - Sales tickets. 2nd run, 1958-1970. (Box 2 of 11), 1958-1959 (Offsite-box 140)
      This box holds 4 stacks: tickets 2000-2999 (Nov 1958-March 1959), 3000-3999 (Jan 1959-April 1959), 4000-4999 (Jan 1959-June 1959), 5000-5999 (May 1959-August 1959).
    - Sales tickets. 2nd run, 1958-1970. (Box 3 of 11), 1959-1960 (Offsite-box 141)
      This box holds 4 stacks: tickets 6000-6999 (July 1959-Oct 1959), 7000-7999 (Oct 1959-Dec 1959), 8000-8999 (Dec 1959-April 1960), 9000-9999 (Jan 1960-August 1960).
    - Sales tickets. 2nd run, 1958-1970. (Box 4 of 11), 1960-1961 (Offsite-box 142)
      This box holds 4 stacks: tickets 10000-10999 (April 1960-Oct 1960), 11000-11999 (May 1960-Oct 1960), 12000-12999 (April 1960-Dec 1960), 13000-13999 (Oct 1960-Jan 1961).
    - Sales tickets. 2nd run, 1958-1970. (Box 5 of 11), 1960-1961 (Offsite-box 143)
      This box holds 5 stacks: tickets 14000-14999 (Dec 1960-April 1961), 15000-15999 (Feb 1961-May 1961), 16000-16999 (May 1961-August 1961), 17000-17751 (July 1961-Oct 1961) (this pack includes a note that ticket book 17752-17999 was destroyed), and 18000-18099 (Sept 1961-Oct 1961). There is then a gap with no tickets numbered 18100-20100. There are also no pink copies of these and there appears to be no chronological gap in the records, so it seems likely that these ticket numbers were never used rather than that they were used but not included in the collection.
    - Sales tickets. 2nd run, 1958-1970. (Box 6 of 11), 1961-1962 (Offsite-box 144)
      This box holds 4 stacks: tickets 20101-20999 (Oct 1961-Dec 1961), 21000-21999 (Dec 1961-July 1962), 22000-22999 (Feb 1962-May 1962), 23000-23999 (May 1962-July 1962).
    - Sales tickets. 2nd run, 1958-1970. (Box 7 of 11), 1962-1963 (Offsite-box 145)
      This box holds 4 stacks: tickets 24000-24999 (June 1962-Sept 1962), 25000-25999 (Sept 1962-Dec 1962), 26000-26999 (Dec 1962-March 1963), 27000-27999 (Feb 1963-June 1963).
    - Sales tickets. 2nd run, 1958-1970. (Box 8 of 11), 1963-1964 (Offsite-box 146)
      This box holds 4 stacks: tickets 28000-28999 (May 1963-Sept 1963), 29000-29999 (May 1963-Dec 1963), 30000-30999 (Nov 1963-March 1964), 31000-31999 (Feb 1964-June 1964).
    - Sales tickets. 2nd run, 1958-1970. (Box 9 of 11), 1964-1965 (Offsite-box 147)
      This box holds 4 stacks: tickets 32000-32999 (June 1964-Oct 1964), 33000-33999 (Sept 1964-Feb 1965), 34000-34999 (Dec 1964-June 1965), 35000-35999 (June 1965-Dec 1965).
    - Sales tickets. 2nd run, 1958-1970. (Box 10 of 11), 1965-1967 (Offsite-box 148)
      This box holds 4 stacks: tickets 36000-36999 (Sept 1965-May 1966), 37000-37999 (May 1966-Dec 1966), 38000-38999 (Nov 1966-May 1967), 39000-39999 (April 1967-Nov 1967).
    - Sales tickets. 2nd run, 1958-1970. (Box 11 of 11), 1967-1970 (Offsite-box 149)
      This box holds the final 4 stacks of tickets comprising the main copies of the 2nd run: tickets 40000-40999 (Nov 1967-July 1968), 41000-41999 (June 1968-April 1969), 42000-42999 (March 1969-Dec 1969), 43000-43664 (Dec 1969-June 1970).
    - Sales tickets. 2nd run, 1958-1970, pink copy. (Box 1 of 9) (Offsite-box 149)
      This box begins the pink (duplicate) copies of the 2nd run sales tickets. This box holds 1 stack: tickets 100-1499 (1958).
    - Sales tickets. 2nd run, 1958-1970, pink copy. (Box 2 of 9), 1958-1959 (Offsite-box 150)
      This box holds 3 stacks: tickets 1500-3099 (1958-59), 3100-4699 (1959), 4700-6299 (1959).
    - Sales tickets. 2nd run, 1958-1970, pink copy. (Box 3 of 9), 1959-1960 (Offsite-box 151)
      This box holds 3 stacks: tickets 6300-8599 (1959), 8600-9699 (1960), 9700-10699 (1960).
    - Sales tickets. 2nd run, 1958-1970, pink copy. (Box 4 of 9), 1960-1961 (Offsite-box 152)
      This box holds 4 stacks: tickets 10700-11699 (1960), 11700-12599 (1960), 12600-13399 (1960), 13403-14699 (1960-61).
    - Sales tickets. 2nd run, 1958-1970, pink copy. (Box 5 of 9), 1961 (Offsite-box 153)
      This box holds 4 stacks: tickets 14700-15899 (1961), 15900-17099 (1961), 17100-18099 (1961), and 20101-21499 (1961-62). As with the main copies of the 2nd run, there are no tickets for 18100-20100.
    - Sales tickets. 2nd run, 1958-1970, pink copy. (Box 6 of 9), 1962 (Offsite-box 154)
      This box holds 4 stacks: tickets 21500-22600 (1962), 22601-23699 (1962), 23700-24799 (1962), 24800-25899 (1962).
    - Sales tickets. 2nd run, 1958-1970, pink copy. (Box 7 of 9), 1962-1964 (Offsite-box 155)
      This box holds 4 stacks: tickets 26000-27299 (1962-63), 27300-28799 (1963), 28800-29999 (1963), 30000-31399 (1963-64).
    - Sales tickets. 2nd run, 1958-1970, pink copy. (Box 8 of 9), 1964-1965 (Offsite-box 156)
      This box holds 4 stacks: tickets 31400-32799 (1964), 32800-33999 (1964-65), 34000-34999 (1964-65), 35000-35999 (1965).
    - Sales tickets. 2nd run, 1958-1970, pink copy. (Box 9 of 9), 1965-1970 (Offsite-box 157)
      This box holds 2 stacks: tickets 36000-36999 (1965-66) and 37000-37999 (1966). The box also holds the final pink copies from the 2nd run, numbers 38000-43664 (1966-70), but these are unorganized and loose in the box.
  - Subseries V.C. Client Invoices, 1946-1970; 26 Linear feet
    The subseries includes copies of the bills Robert Ensko Inc sent to their clients. Information on the invoices include customer name and address, item(s) or services (repairs, engravings) purchased, price, and shipping.
    The subseries is in original order, which is by sequence number of the invoice, which in turn is roughly chronological by invoice date.
    - Client invoices, 1946-1947 (Offsite-box 160)
      This box holds three stacks of bills numbered 101-2300 (June 1946-Dec 1946), 2301-3300 (Dec 1946-March 1947), 3301-4700 (March 1947-August 1947).
    - Client invoices, 1947-1948 (Offsite-box 161)
      This box holds three stacks of bills numbered 4701-6078 (August 1947-Dec 1947), 6079-7215 (Jan 1948-April 1948), 7216-8300 (May 1948-August 1948).
    - Client invoices, 1948-1949 (Offsite-box 162)
      This box holds an unopened packet of loose bills, labeled Sept 1948-Dec 1948; these are presumably numbered 8301-10007. The box then holds two stacks of bills numbered 10008-10865 (Jan 1949-March 1949) and 10866-11837 (April 1949-June 1949).
    - Client invoices, 1949-1950 (Offsite-box 163)
      The box holds three stacks of bills numbered 11838-13607 (July 1949-Dec 1949), 13608-14753 (Jan 1950-April 1950), 14754-16126 (May 1950-August 1950).
    - Client invoices, 1950-1951 (Offsite-box 164)
      The box holds three stacks of bills numbered 16127-17960 (Sept 1950-Dec 1950), 17961-19551 (Jan 1951-April 1951), 19552-21078 (May 1951-August 1951).
    - Client invoices, 1951-1952 (Offsite-box 165)
      The box holds three stacks of bills numbered 21079-22332 (Sept 1951-Nov 1951), 22333-23741 (Dec 1951-Feb 1952), 23742-24913 (March 1952-May 1952).
    - Client invoices, 1952-1953 (Offsite-box 166)
      The box holds three stacks of bills numbered 24914-26179 (June 1952-Sept 1952), 26180-27759 (Oct 1952-Dec 1952), 27760-29202 (Jan 1953-April 1953).
    - Client invoices, 1953-1954 (Offsite-box 167)
      The box holds three stacks of bills numbered 29203-30549 (May 1953-July 1953), 30550-32637 (August 1953-Dec 1953), 32638-34114 (Jan 1954-April 1954).
    - Client invoices, 1954-1955 (Offsite-box 168)
      The box holds three stacks of bills numbered 34115-35670 (May 1954-August 1954), 35671-37732 (Sept 1954-Dec 1954), 37733-38869 (Jan 1955-March 1955).
    - Client invoices, 1955 (Offsite-box 169)
      The box holds three stacks of bills numbered 38870-40302 (April 1955-June 1955), 40303-41582 (July 1955-Oct 1955), 41583-42808 (Nov 1955-Dec 1955).
    - Client invoices, 1956 (Offsite-box 170)
      The box holds three stacks of bills numbered 42809-43890 (Jan 1956-March 1956), 43891-45287 (April 1956-June 1956), 45288-46384 (July 1956-Sept 1956).
    - Client invoices, 1956-1957 (Offsite-box 171)
      The box holds three stacks of bills numbered 46365-47855 (Oct 1956-Dec 1956), 47856-49192 (Jan 1957-March 1957), 49193-50670 (April 1957-June 1957).
    - Client invoices, 1957-1958 (Offsite-box 172)
      The box holds three stacks of bills numbered 50671-51691 (July 1957-Sept 1957), 51692-53038 (Oct 1957-Dec 1957), 53039-54129 (Jan 1958-March 1958).
    - Client invoices, 1958 (Offsite-box 173)
      The box holds three stacks of bills numbered 54130-55417 (April 1958-June 1958), 55418-56838 (July 1958-Oct 1958), 56839-58009 (Nov 1958-Dec 1958).
    - Client invoices, 1959 (Offsite-box 174)
      The box holds three stacks of bills numbered 58009-59120 (Jan 1959-March 1959), 59121-60489 (April 1959-June 1959), 60490-61872 (July 1959-Oct 1959).
    - Client invoices, 1959-1960 (Offsite-box 175)
      The box holds three stacks of bills numbered 61873-62978 (Nov 1959-Dec 1959), 62979-64391 (Jan 1960-April 1960), 64392-65575 (May 1960-June 1960).
    - Client invoices, 1960-1961 (Offsite-box 176)
      The box holds three stacks of bills numbered 65576-67036 (July 1960-Oct 1960), 67037-68072 (Nov 1960-Dec 1960), 68073-69144 (Jan 1961-March 1961).